You don't need me to teach you how to read.
لست بحاجة لي أن أعلمك القراءة.
Why are you so close?
لماذا انت قريب جدا؟
The smell of toilet water is too strong.
رائحة ماء المرحاض قوية جدا.
you
أنت
Lin Zeyan, wait and see how long you can stay.
لين زيان ، انتظر وشاهد كم من الوقت يمكنك البقاء.
The position of the slipper has changed 30 cm.
تم تغيير موضع النعال 30 سم.
Secretary Li, I just want to ask you something.
معالي الوزير لي ، أريد فقط أن أسألك شيئًا.
Lin Zeyan. No, no.
لين زيان.
Does President Lin have any dietary restrictions?
هل لدى الرئيس لين أي قيود غذائية؟
No, I think he has eaten less recently.
لا ، أعتقد أنه أكل مؤخرًا.
It's not the way to go on like this.
إنها ليست طريقة المضي قدمًا على هذا النحو.
Mr. Lin is very picky.
السيد لين صعب الإرضاء للغاية.
Mr. Lin hates green pepper. He doesn't eat coriander.
السيد لين يكره الفلفل الأخضر.  لا يأكل الكزبرة.
I don't even like mushrooms.
أنا لا أحب حتى الفطر.
You're so picky.
أنت صعب الإرضاء.
If you have conscience, don't say it was me.
إذا كان لديك ضمير ، فلا تقل أنه أنا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I wouldn't have said it was you.
لم أكن لأقول أنه أنت.
It's too late for me to thank you.
لقد فات الأوان بالنسبة لي لأشكرك.
By the way, Lin Zeyan
بالمناسبة ، لين زيان
He seems to know his family very well.
يبدو أنه يعرف عائلته جيدًا.
I can see them.
استطيع ان اراهم.
That's because the location of the house is according to President Lin.
هذا لأن موقع المنزل حسب الرئيس لين.
I'm used to designing.
أنا معتاد على التصميم.
Everything is the same.
كل شيء متشابه.
I'm telling you,
أنا أخبرك،
It's the same as opening it.
إنه نفس فتحه.
This is a new dish.
هذا طبق جديد.
Have a taste.
تذوق.
It must be delicious. Hey.
يجب أن تكون لذيذة.  يا.
Xia You, it seems that you don't want your salary.
شيا يو ، يبدو أنك لا تريد راتبك.
Did you taste it?
هل تذوقته؟
Unless my sense of taste fails.
ما لم يفشل حاسة التذوق لدي.
You are so careless.
أنت مهمل جدا.
sorry
آسف
How dare I do that next time?
كيف أجرؤ على القيام بذلك في المرة القادمة؟
The taste
الطعم
The accident was handled cleanly.
تم التعامل مع الحادث بشكل نظيف.
If it's only made by the touch,
إذا تم فقط عن طريق اللمس ،
You are talented.
أنت موهوب.
It's hard to change the taste completely.
من الصعب تغيير المذاق تمامًا.
Try another way next time.
جرب طريقة أخرى في المرة القادمة.
She did it on purpose.
فعلت ذلك عن قصد.
It seems she can't get away with deducting her salary for a month.
يبدو أنها لا تستطيع أن تفلت من خصم راتبها لمدة شهر.
My eyes hurt.
عيناي تؤلماني.
Open the window and give him some air.
افتح النافذة وامنحه بعض الهواء.
What's wrong with him?
ماذا حل به؟
actually
في الحقيقة
Lin Zeyan looks good with his mouth closed.
يبدو لين زيان جيدًا وفمه مغلق.
President Lin, Xia You was caught by the tabloids.
الرئيس لين ، شيا يو قبضت عليه الصحف.
On the top search list.
في قائمة البحث العليا.
Now the public opinion is everywhere.
الآن الرأي العام في كل مكان.
Is it pretty?
هل هذا جميل؟
good-looking
جميل المظهر
It's a misunderstanding.
إنه سوء فهم.
Get up and change.
انهض وقم بتغيير.
You still have time to dress up.
لا يزال لديك الوقت لارتداء الملابس.
I mean get changed and go to the office with me.
أعني أن تتغير وتذهب معي إلى المكتب.
Ah
آه
Sandy, do me a favor.
ساندي ، اصنع لي معروفا.
Isn't this President Lin's rumored girlfriend?
أليست هذه صديقة الرئيس لين المشاع؟
Why are you leading the company?
لماذا تقود الشركة؟
You brought them out.
لقد أخرجتهم.
Is it her?
أهذه هي؟
Is it the hot topic on Weibo?
هل هو الموضوع الساخن على Weibo؟
President Lin, Sandy wants to meet you.
الرئيس لين ، ساندي تريد مقابلتك.
Seems to be using this scandal
يبدو أنه يستخدم هذه الفضيحة
To bring up the money.
لجلب المال.
What should we do next?
ماذا علينا أن نفعل بعد ذلك؟
Don't worry. Just let her wait.
لا تقلق.  فقط دعها تنتظر.
How about I handle this?
ماذا عن التعامل مع هذا؟
Make me a cup of coffee.
اصنع لي فنجان قهوة.
You don't have to look at him.
ليس عليك أن تنظر إليه.
I won't let you fool him.
لن أدعك تخدعه.
I told you he's not blind at all.
قلت لك إنه ليس أعمى على الإطلاق.
Miss Xia, you scared me to death.
آنسة شيا ، لقد أخفتني حتى الموت.
Take a seat here.
اجلس هنا.
Don't go anywhere.
لا تذهب إلى أي مكان.
I'll get you a cup of coffee.
سأحضر لك فنجان قهوة.
Well
نحن سوف
I've been working in Solai Cafe.
لقد كنت أعمل في مقهى Solai.
For more than two hours.
لأكثر من ساعتين.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
I'll go to your company if I don't come.
سأذهب إلى شركتك إذا لم أحضر.
Mr. Lin, Miss Xia is gone.
السيد لين ، الآنسة شيا ذهبت.
It's okay. I know.
حسنا.  أنا أعرف.
Hello
مرحبًا
Is this Miss Sandy?
هل هذه ملكة جمال ساندي؟